paiskincare.com 2014-07-03

# Privacy Policy : Pai Skincare, Organic Solutions for Sensitive Skin

## Your Privacy

At Pai, we take great care to protect the privacy of our site visitors and customers.

We are customers ourselves of other Internet Retail sites and and fully appreciate and respect the importance of privacy on the Internet. We will not disclose information about our customers to third parties except where it is part of providing a service to you - e.g. arranging for a product to be sent to you - or where we have your express permission to do so. 

## Your Consent

We will not sell your name, address, e-mail address, credit card information or personal information to any third party.

## Communication & Marketing

If you have opted to receive newsletter communications, we may occasionally update you on our latest products, news and special offers via e-mail & post.

You have the option to opt-out of receiving marketing communications from us. If you do not wish to continue to receive marketing from us you should opt-out by clicking the "unsubscribe" button at the top of every email newsletter communication or use our [Unsubscribe Form](http://paiskincare.list-manage.com/unsubscribe?u=378d44c62328202143f216a21&id=a3237af4f3).

## Real Time Personal Emails / Transactional Emails

We email every customer confirmation of their order details and order dispatch information. You can opt out of receiving real time personal emails by clicking the Opt Out link at the bottom of these emails. Please note, that by doing so, you will not receive order or delivery notifications, password reset emails and returns emails. 

## Financial Information

Pai does not collect or store **any** type of sensitive financial information about our customers. This includes credit card details, bank account information or PayPal credentials. All payment processing is handled off-site by our bank and credit card processor. This information is encrypted and sent using industry standard SSL security technology (the same method other e-commerce websites and banks use).

## Cookie/Tracking Technology

The site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the site, and understanding how visitors use the site. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties, including our site analytics partner, [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/), and our affiliate marketing partner, [Affiliate Window Ltd](http://www.affiliatewindow.com/).

## Commitment to Data Security

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential, for example, our Accountants or Auditors) have access to this information. 

## Customer Information

Pai retains personally identifiable information about our customers necessary to process orders as well as to speed up repeat purchases at our website.

Pai Skincare Limited (at the address below) is the data controller for the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the Act).

The information we collect is always provided voluntarily by you and includes:

  * Your name
  * Your billing address
  * Your delivery address
  * Your contact details, including telephone and email information so that we or our delivery partners may contact you to advise you of order dispatch and to arrange deliveries.

You may view and amend any of this information from the "My Account" section on the Pai website.

This information is encrypted using industry standard SSL technologies and only accessible using the login and password details you set on registering an account.

We would strongly recommend that you do not use the browser's password memory function as that would permit other people using your terminal to access your personal information.

If you wish to verify or correct any of the information we hold about you, you can do so using the "My Account" section or by contacting us using the details below.

## Contacting Us

We are always pleased to hear from our customers - even if it is a complaint! We are always grateful for any time you spend providing us with the knowledge we need to ensure our customers are completely satisfied - we want you to return to the site and to recommend us to your friends and family. If you have any questions or feedback about this statement, or if you would like us to stop processing your information, please do not hesitate to contact us and we will be delighted to answer any questions you may have. 

You can either contact [customer services](http://www.paiskincare.com/pages/contact-us-155). 

Or, write to us at: 

Pai Skincare Ltd  
18 Colville Road  
London W3 8BL  
UK
